[boys chatting]
- [boy 1] Oh my God, this is…
- [boy 2] …on the lower side, okay?
[boy 3 whispers] It's him!
Do you think it's actually true?
- [boy 4] Yeah right, stop bullshitting.
- [boy 5] I'm gonna ask him.
Is the rumor real?
Rumor?
We heard that Ahn Su-ho, Yeon Si-eun,
and you caught some gangsters.
The Free Money guy.
Uh, uh-huh.
- Are you freaking serious?
- Oh, whoa.
[boy 6] Yeah, my friend lost
millions of won from that app.
So what happened? Tell us everything.
- [boy 5] Beom-seok-a, gimme your IG.
- [boy 6] Tell us! I'm dying to know.
[boys laughing and chattering outside]
[Beom-seok sighs]
Did you get home okay?
Yeah, I did.
- [chair scrapes]
- You?
- I got home all right too.
- [boy 7] …got kidnapped.
- Then Si-eun brought the police.
- [boy 8] Don't tell them…
You thought they were scared?
[chair scraping]
[paper rustling]
[sighs]
[Jeong-chan sighs]
[Su-ho] All right!
[sighs]
[grunts]
Aah.
[quirky music playing]
- You're gonna eat all that?
- Yeah. Then I'm going to the snack bar.
- Right, Oh Beom?
- [Beom-seok] Mm-hmm. My treat.
- You should come.
- [Su-ho] Nah, you always do.
Today it's my treat. Get what you want.
It's going to be killer. Get ready.
Are you guys free this weekend?
I found this awesome restaurant. Let's go.
Sounds like something I'd like.
I'm in. Let's go.
Um, why talk about food
when you're eating?
What about you? You talk about life
while you're still living it.
[chuckles]
Oh, what about Yeong-i's job?
[Su-ho] Her interview's this weekend.
We're short-staffed, so it works out.
- Who's Yeong-i?
- [Su-ho] That girl.
The… the one
who bashed Gil-su on the head.
Oh.
- Were you both already friends?
- No.
Uh, she's staying
at Su-ho's place for a while.
Should we invite her this weekend?
Sure, that's fine with me.
Yeah, invite her.
[Su-ho groans]
[sighs]
AHN SU-HO
FOLLOWING
[tense music playing]
YEONG-I
CHILLING AT HAN RIVER
DINNER WITH SU-HO'S GRANDMA
SI-EUN SURPRISED US WITH TASTY HAMBURGERS!
[elegant piano music playing]
[sighs]
[chuckles] How is he?
Dad's been busy. The season.
Huh.
Have you decided your path?
Not yet.
It's all right to take time to decide.
I'm not worried about your career path.
You're always good at everything.
[mother chuckles]
There's a lot I can't do.
Hmm?
[Si-eun sighs]
- Nothing.
- [phone buzzing]
[gasps]
Hey, almost finished?
We can get coffee on our way.
I have a meeting.
[buzzing continues]
[mother] Hello?
I'm on my way.
[Yeong-i] What do you wanna do
on your birthday?
What do you think?
Nothing special.
- We can meet up, have something to eat.
- [Beom-seok] Well--
- Watch it.
- [Yeong-i] Come on. We can't do nothing.
We gotta have a lot of fun.
Ugh, we don't have to, ajumma-ya.
Oh, when's your birthday?
[Yeong-i] Saturday two weeks from now.
- Wanna rent a party room?
- Ajumma.
Aren't you saving money? Huh?
I thought you were trying to rent a room.
[Beom-seok chuckles]
[light muzak playing]
[woman] Yeah, that's our order.
[Yeong-i] Ah, the menu's stacked.
What should I get?
What would you like?
[Su-ho] Iced Americano for me.
I want an iced Vienna.
Let's get a table.
This one looks good, right?
Come sit over here.
- [cashier] Would you like to order?
- [Yeong-i] Hey. Give me a thousand won.
- [Su-ho] I don't have it.
- Yes, please. Here.
[register whirs]
[sighs]
[melancholy music playing]
[shop bell rings]
[Yeong-i] Hey, Si-eun-a!
Hey, hurry and come sit.
What? Why are you so dressed up today?
Did you think I'd be into that?
- [chuckles] You're so smart.
- [Su-ho] Where have you been?
[Si-eun] Hmm? You don't need to know.
I just had a thing.
[Yeong-i] A thing? What thing?
[Su-ho] Hey, he's a super sus kinda guy.
[Yeong-i] I already know
where Si-eun's been.
- Stop keeping track of me.
- [Yeong-i] No way.
I have to watch to see when you get home.
[Su-ho] Good idea. Check in on him.
- Do you know what WithMap is?
- [Su-ho] No idea.
Hey, Oh Beom. Hey.
["Hero" by Meego playing]
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
[Su-ho singing in Korean]
Want a drink?
- Hmm?
- Want a drink?
- Sure. Should I come?
- No, I'll go by myself.
[Su-ho and Yeong-i
continue singing in Korean]
Hey! Oh Beom-seok.
- [boy 1] Oh Beom-seok?
- [boy 2] Hey!
- [boy 1] Beom-seok? Why would he be here?
- [boy 2] It was him.
- [boy 1] Stop shitting me.
- [boy 2] I really saw him.
Hey!
- [boy 3] Did he see us and run off?
- [boy 2] Beom-seok-jjang, where are you?
[boy 3] He sings too?
- [boy 1] Oh Beom-seok!
- [boy 2] Hey, call his phone.
Shit.
[sighs]
Yeah, we're at karaoke.
The room number?
[Su-ho] Dunno.
- Hey, your friends keep calling you.
- [gasps]
You stupid bitch! What the hell, huh?
Why did you pick up my phone
without asking? Fuck!
Hey, man, what's wrong?
Are you gonna hit me or what?
Fuck you.
I will seriously fucking kill you.
- I swear to God…
- [Su-ho] Hey, that's enough.
What's with you, man?
[Beom-seok breathing shakily]
- You dumb fuck.
- [Su-ho] Beom-seok-a.
I said that's enough.
Fuck this, you stupid crazy asshole.
Fuck off.
[Su-ho] Hey. Hey!
[sighs] I'll go after her.
Where are you going?
- [sighs] Are you okay?
- [door closes]
Yeah.
- Fine.
- [door opens]
Hey, Beom-seok-a.
I told you that I saw him!
- [boy 3] Fuck, you were right.
- [boy 2] Wow, my Beom-seok-jjang!
- [giggling]
- [boy 4] How you been, Beom-seok-a?
- It's really been a while.
- [boy 3] Damn, man.
[boy 4] We missed you, dude.
[boy 3] We missed you, man.
What?
We're Beom-seok's friends.
[tense music playing]
We were talking.
- [boy 2 giggles]
- It's just been so long.
We wanted to talk too.
Then do it later.
[boys giggling]
Sorry about that.
Let's hang soon.
I'll call you.
Make sure you pick up.
Let's go.
- [boy 2] See ya.
- [boy 3] Man.
- Still looks like a loser.
- [boy 2] Fun.
What was that?
- [Beom-seok] Huh?
- Those guys.
Oh.
[sighs] It's no big deal.
[lively conversation]
- [vocalizing]
- [laughing]
[boy 1] Come on!
- Oh, man!
- [man singing on video]
[boys laughing loudly]
[boy 1] His tongue's moving so fast,
but he sounds like a freaking dumbass.
- [boy 2] We should be here all day.
- [boy 1] All day, every day.
- [laughter continues]
- Hey.
[boy 2] Do it again, one more time!
Hey!
[silence]
Quiet.
What's his problem?
- I was just trying to be funny.
- You were funny.
Shut your mouths.
[scoffs]
[chair clatters]
[Beom-seok] Did you laugh?
I didn't laugh.
- [chair clatters]
- I heard you laughing.
Do you wanna die, you fucking prick?
[footsteps]
[Si-eun] Hey, Beom-seok.
What's wrong?
[boy 1 scoffs]
Dude's being a dick
'cause Su-ho and Si-eun are on his side.
- What?
- [chair scrapes]
[Su-ho] Hey, move.
What is it? What's going on? Hm?
He flipped out for, like, no reason!
- Fuck you. I'll kill you, asshole.
- Hey, that's enough. Enough. Hey.
- What the fuck are you looking at? Huh?
- [Su-ho] Why do you try to be so tough?
It's kinda cute.
Si-eun-a. Cafeteria. Food.
Stop putting your arm around me.
Huh?
[Beom-seok sighs]
[students murmuring]
What's gotten into him?
[scoffs]
[tense music playing]
[Beom-seok groans]
[moans]
[inaudible]
[phone buzzes]
FUCKER 3
15 MISSED CALLS
16 MISSED CALLS
FUCKER 4
[buzzing continues]
17 MISSED CALLS
[phone chimes]
[panting]
[Su-ho] How was it?
Feeling refreshed
from your early morning workout?
[Si-eun scoffs]
[Su-ho] Did you get in touch with Oh Beom?
- [Si-eun] No.
- Is there something going on with him?
He won't pick up his phone.
Wanna swing by his place later?
Yeah, let's go see him.
All right. Stand up.
You told me to just run. There's more?
I said I'd give you a lesson.
Hmm? We'll do just the basics.
[grunts]
Stand with your feet shoulder width apart.
The tip of your feet point diagonally.
You can stop anytime.
You have to be tired. Go home and sleep.
I'm not tired, don't worry. Come on.
[soft guitar music playing]
[sighs]
Make sure you always tuck in your chin.
Okay?
Arms like this.
You have to use your arms to protect
your chin at all times. Don't forget.
Chin. That's it.
Next, imagine
there's a punk in front of you.
He's threatening to beat you to death,
you're not gonna live, etcetera.
When this happens,
you don't want to look into his eyes.
Look at his shoulders instead.
Watch me.
Keep your eyes on his shoulders.
Then, when his shoulder comes
toward your face,
duck below at a 90-degree angle
and then grab!
In this pose,
grab his knees and push him over.
- One, two, three.
- [Si-eun sighs]
That's called a takedown.
The next step is
to take your fists and beat…
Never mind. Run.
It's better just to run.
Run away while the other guy's down
because you might get hurt fighting him.
[sighs] Got it?
[Su-ho] This is it?
He lives in a freaking nice place.
[lock bleeps]
What are you guys doing here?
Dude, why did you turn your phone off?
[sighs] Oh, I didn't know it was off.
Come in.
[Su-ho] What about school? Huh?
Why'd you no-show? Hmm?
Your place is sick.
- [Beom-seok] I wasn't feeling well.
- [look bleeps]
- Put those on.
- [Su-ho] Nice.
This is probably why you're so thin.
Lose weight just walking
around your house.
[gasps]
This place is huge.
Is this the famous ZZ plant
that's supposed to bring in
a lot of money and wealth?
Huh?
Hmm? This is amazing!
This room's gigantic.
Bigger than my house.
Do you feel really ill?
No, not too bad. Just some.
[Su-ho] Hey, your mother's
really beautiful.
It's great seeing your family so happy.
You all look alike. Hmm.
We aren't family.
My father adopted me publicly
when he got into politics.
It was a publicity stunt.
[sighs]
[sighs] You guys want a drink?
- Is something wrong?
- [Su-ho] Aah.
- No, nothing's wrong.
- Hey, what is it? Hmm?
It's okay. You can tell me anything.
[Si-eun] Maybe…
Is it because of those guys at karaoke?
- Is it them?
- [Su-ho] Karaoke?
What karaoke?
[tense music playing]
- [laughter]
- [boy 1] Stay right there.
[Beom-seok grunts]
- [boy 2] Hey, move over.
- [laughter]
[boy 2] At ease.
I said stand at ease, you freaking mutt.
[boy 3] Hurry the hell up.
- [Beom-seok panting]
- Did you forget?
- I told you to stand.
- [boy 2] Here I come.
- [boy 3] Give it everything.
- [boy 1] Show him what you've got!
- [boy 3] Pow! Nice job!
- [boy 4] Yes, that's it!
[boy 4 laughs]
- [boy 3] Are you crying?
- [boy 1] Fuck you.
- Stop pretending it hurts.
- [boy 3] Hey, hey.
Beom-seok-a,
you better not tell your dad, okay?
- [sobbing]
- [boy 2] Hey, let's go.
- It's no fucking fun beating him up.
- [boy 4] I'm starving. Let's get food.
- [boy 3] Yeah, I'm hungry too.
- [boy 1] Ugh, that was so boring.
- A total waste of time.
- [all laughing]
[Beom-seok] At my former school…
I was bullied.
And because of them…
[breathing shakily]
…I ended up in the hospital
and transferred schools to here.
But then, ever since
they ran into me at karaoke,
they won't stop calling,
telling me to come out.
[Su-ho] Oh, fuck.
Why'd those fucking assholes
do that to you?
Huh?
What did you even do wrong?
Sometimes it just happens.
In order to move up
in their group of friends,
they pick someone to bully.
What did I do wrong?
I didn't do anything to provoke it.
It's okay, Beom-seok-a.
It wasn't your fault.
[poignant music playing]
Call those dickheads right now.
What?
I'll make them apologize to ya.
Give 'em a call.
- [pop music playing]
- [laughter]
[singing in Korean]
- [boy 1] Did you swallow a frog?
- [shrieking with laughter]
[boy 2] He's so freaking bad.
Like, the worst.
[boy 3 continues singing]
MUTT BEOM-SEOK
- Hey, hey, hey!
- [boy 1] Hey!
- Why did you turn it off?
- [boy 3] What the hell?
- Our little Beom-seok's calling back.
- [bleep]
Oh, what? Seriously?
- Guys, shut up. Damn it.
- Beom-seok-jjang?
Hey, Beom-seok-a. Where are ya?
[pop music playing in bar]
[sighs] Why are these pricks always
at karaoke when they should be studying?
You're really one to talk.
Don't be scared. I got you.
[muffled, overlapping
karaoke tracks playing]
[pop track playing]
[boy 1 singing in Korean]
Oh! Beom-seok's here.
- [boy 2] Hey, Oh Beom. You actually came.
- [boy 3] You brought your friends?
- [Su-ho] Fuck this.
- [boy 3] He's scary!
The fucking cigarettes reek. [sniffs]
[boy 4 laughs]
What the hell's this?
Apologize.
Apologize to me.
- [laughing]
- [boy 1] Right.
You hear that?
Apologize for what?
For everything that you've done.
Hey, Beom-seok-a.
We apologize
when something we do is wrong.
We're friends, Beom-seok-a.
Aren't we?
I mean, we had fun together.
What's your deal?
Huh?
Hey.
- Apologize correctly.
- [boy 4] What?
How many times do we have to say it?
Apologize to him before I kick your ass,
okay? Don't mess around.
[sighs] Beom-seok-a.
What the fuck do you think
that you're doing?
Do you wanna go back to being friends?
See each other every day?
Ah! Ah!
- Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
- [Su-ho] Did you forget I was here?
Hey! Hey, wait. Wait a sec. Wait a sec.
- [Su-ho] Apologize properly.
- [boy 4] Fine! I get it.
- [Su-ho] Answer me.
- Ow! Okay, okay! I said I fucking get it!
[groans]
[Su-ho] Hey. Do it now.
[boy 4 scoffs]
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
If you're sorry…
[breathing shakily]
…then let me hit you.
[boy 4] What?
You're bullshitting your apology to me,
so let me hit you.
[boy 4 scoffs]
- [Su-ho] Okay, then.
- [sighs]
Let him hit you and move on.
[suspenseful music playing]
[sighs]
Honestly, really, truly, I'm so fucking
super sorry, all right, Beom-seok-a?
[grunts]
[coughs]
What the fuck?
You crazy shithead. Fuck you!
Hey, are you okay?
[boy 4] Hey.
[breathing unsteadily]
- [feedback shrieks]
- [Si-eun] Hey. Hey!
[Su-ho, muffled] Hey.
That's enough.
Don't cross the line.
Hey. Hey!
- Enough's enough.
- Fuck, let go of me, you fucking asshole!
Let go of me, you bitch. Fucking asshole!
[feedback shrieks]
Fuck it. Come here,
you shit for brains! Fuck!
[Si-eun sighs]
What the fuck was that?
[Si-eun] None of you
ever contact Beom-seok again.
- [Beom-seok] Fuck.
- [Su-ho] Come here.
Hey, stop. [gasping]
I can't br…
[sobbing] I can't breathe.
[sighs] Okay, man. I'm sorry. Sorry.
Stop doing that!
Stop putting your arm around my shoulder.
Why do you fucking drag me
around everywhere?
- What?
- Why are you always ordering me around?
Huh? Why do I fucking have to stop
because you decided? Huh?
Those fucking assholes put me
through so much shit.
You have no idea.
When have I ever ordered you around?
[Beom-seok] You fucking
order me around every day.
Do I have to stop when you tell me to?
Am I your fucking minion?
[Su-ho] Hey.
Did I do something to you?
I skipped on my part-time job to help
you out. Why the hell are you bitching?
- [Beom-seok] Unbelievable.
- [Si-eun] Hey, come on.
[Beom-seok] To help me out?
You're patronizing me, seriously?
Do you want me to pay you
for missing work?
[Su-ho] You're being a fucking asshole.
Say that to me one more time.
Try running your mouth again, you fuck.
Hey, let go and talk it out.
Huh?
[Beom-seok breathing shakily]
Fuck this.
Hey, Beom-seok-a.
- [Su-ho sighs] That nut job.
- [door closes]
I'll go talk to him.
[sighs]
[door opens]
[music thumping from bars]
[laughter and chatting]
[Si-eun] Beom-seok-a.
What's gotten into you?
Are you okay?
[sighs]
Yeah, I'm fine.
See you later.
[phone buzzing]
- Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
- [boy 1] Hey.
This fucking asshole!
[bleep]
[ringing tone]
[boys laughing]
[Tae-hun] What the hell's with this prick?
- You're such a dipshit.
- Huh?
Oh Beom-seok?
You took your glasses off.
[Tae-hun] You, uh, hang out here too?
[boy 2] Hey, Oh Beom-seok!
Follow me.
[Jeong-chan] Hey, where you from?
- Mungang?
- [Tae-hun] Ahh!
Rich kids, right?
[all laugh]
I said follow me, you fucking bastard.
Man, this wuss from Mungang's trying
to mess with Byuksan.
Wanna die?
I was so broke, but it's my lucky day!
Hey, how much you got?
[Tae-hun] Hey, bro, don't be scared.
Let's have a quick chat.
- [slap]
- [Tae-hun] I heard that one.
- Next!
- [Jeong-chan] You prick.
Raise your fuckin' head.
- Sit upright, you dipshit.
- [boys] Ooh!
- [laughter]
- [Jeong-chan] You too. Lift your head.
- [Tae-hun] Sit up.
- [Jeong-chan] Hey.
You should've fucking stuck
to your studies. Why pick a fight?
Fuck. Okay. Time to pull out your phones.
- [shoe squeaks]
- [boy 3 grunts]
667-502.
118-4117.
Lee Jeong-chan.
- [sighs]
- [Tae-hun] How much we get?
- Damn it. We found a bunch of broke asses.
- I'll fucking kick your ass.
- [Tae-hun] That sucks.
- Bitch.
[dramatic music playing]
You're the bitch! Asshole!
What the fuck are you looking at? Huh?
Spit it out!
Do you have something to say,
you fucking asshole?
You son of a bitch. You fucking asshole.
- Fuck you, asshole. Goddamn motherfucker.
- He's totally lost it.
[whimpers]
If you're kicking his ass,
make sure you do it right. Go all in.
[laughter]
- [Tae-hun] Yeah! That's it.
- Asshole! Shit!
- [Tae-hun] Little bro's goin' hard!
- Die, you stupid fucking shit fuck!
[panting]
Fuck you.
Say that to my face one more time, fucker.
[kick lands]
[music fades]
[panting]
You done? Let's go for a drink.
Sure.
[loud techno music playing]
[crowd cheering]
Hey, man, come on, dance!
- [Tae-hun] That one? Damn, the girl was…
- [Jeong-chan] Go hit on someone.
[Tae-hun] Gotta get wasted
for girls like that.
- How much money you guys have on you?
- [boy 1] Nothing.
- How much did you get from those pricks?
- [Jeong-chan] We're out after the drinks.
Hey, forget it.
There's too many of us to hit on girls.
[Tae-hun] Damn it, for real, bro.
Drinks are on me. Order what you want.
- [Jeong-chan] What?
- [Tae-hun] Bro, what?
- So much money!
- [all gasping]
- Wow!
- My man!
- Oh!
- [Tae-hun chants] Oh Beom-seok!
- [Jeong-chan] Go!
- [all] Oh Beom-seok!
- [boy 2] Let's drink, then talk!
- [all] Oh Beom-seok! Oh Beom-seok!
- [boy 2] Sweet!
- [Jeong-chan] Everybody, selfie!
[Tae-hun] Lift it up, show the cash!
- [Jeong-chan] One, two.
- [Tae-hun] Nice shot!
[all] Cheers!
- [boy 3] Drink up!
- [Tae-hun] Yeah!
- [boy 2] Aah!
- [Tae-hun] Aah!
- [Jeong-chan] Look for pretty girls.
- Oh shit, 500,000 won!
- Do you like it?
- [boy 3] It's smooth!
- Yeah, it's good.
- All right.
- [boy 3] Rich drinks taste better.
- [Jeong-chan] Hmm.
Beom-seok-a, what's your IG?
So I can tag you.
Oh.
- I'll follow you if you follow me.
- [Jeong-chan] Sure.
- All done.
- Cool.
- [boy 3] Hey, over there.
- [Tae-hun] Yeah, where?
Oh! Hey, come with me.
- [boy 2] Not him. Take him.
- [boy 4] I'm bad at this.
- I can't.
- [boy 3] Fuck it. You. Let's go.
- Ping!
- [boy 4] Make sure you succeed.
- [boy 2] He's insane.
- [Jeong-chan] Hey, forget him.
- Let's cheers. Cheers, cheers.
- [boy 2] Let's go!
- [Beom-seok] Cheers.
- [boy 2] Let's go! Let's go!
Wow, dude, that's a lot.
[all] Ohh!
- You'll get shit-faced!
- Dude, that drink is so strong.
[all cheering]
- Beom-seok, let's go!
- Let's get a girl for Beom-seok.
Where's a girl that Beom-seok would like?
- Ooh, what about that one?
- [boy 2] Oh yeah.
- [boy 4] No, she's ugly.
- [Jeong-chan] You have high standards.
- [boy 2] You turn everyone down.
- [boy 4] Look around, okay?
[Jeong-chan] What about her?
Fuck. She's so pretty. That one, yeah.
AHN SU-HO
- [boy 2] Hey, what are you--
- [Jeong-chan] Wait, which one?
- [server] Here are your drinks.
- [Jeong-chan] Thank you. Point her out.
UNFOLLOW
- [Jeong-chan] Where, where?
- [boy 2] Just go try!
[Jeong-chan laughs] They failed!
Hey!
- Salute.
- [boy 2 and 4] Fail!
- [boy 2] She humbled your ass.
- [boy 4] What was that?
Nah, nah, nah. When I saw her up close,
she wasn't my type.
- [Jeong-chan] Did you even try?
- [boy 3] No, she was fucking ugly.
- [Jeong-chan] Forget it.
- [Tae-hun] He couldn't get a word out.
[Jeong-chan] Come here,
loser who couldn't say a word. Give up!
- Have another drink.
- [boy 3] Can you pour me a lot of beer?
- [boy 2] Whoa, I'm reaching my limit.
- [Jeong-chan] You can't be drunk already.
Hmm?
Oh! Uh, where is he going?
- Where are you going?
- Beom-seok-a!
Wanna party?
What?
Come party with us.
[chuckles]
- [Jeong-chan] What?
- [all exclaiming]
Bro's got more rizz than you do!
[club music fading]
[moody, ambient music playing]
[moody music continues]
ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND EVENTS
ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL